SUHAAS MOHANDOS

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Talented software development professional with experience (total: 13+ years, relevant:8+ years) in Java & Spring boot based applications. Consistent in delivering clean, error-free, reliable code to meet current or expected needs. Well-versed in software trends and confident in multiple languages, frameworks and programming tools.

Work Experience:

Wipro(Dec 2014 - Present)

Senior Software Engineer

PSD(Payment Service Directive)

1. PSD(Payment Service Directive) provides two services namely AIS (Account Information Services) and PIS(Payment Information Services)

Roles & Responsibilities:

- 1. Designed and implemented microservices that communicate with each other.
- 2. Unit testing of the code by using Junit and Mockito.
- 3. Followed agile process.

PD

1. PD is about mathematical calculation for counterparties.

Roles & Responsibilities:

- 1. Designed and implemented microservices that communicate with each other.
- 2. Unit testing of the code by using Junit and Mockito.
- 3. Followed agile process.

Exilant Technologies(Oct 2013 - Dec 2014)

Programmer Analyst

RAI (Risk Analytics Infrastructure)

1. Risk Analytics is a high level infrastructure, which hosts models.

Roles & Responsibilities:

1. Designed and Implemented rest based API's with end to end software development life cycle(SDLC).

Mindtree(May 2010 - Oct 2013)

Software Engineer

Defence Research Development Organisation(DRDO)

1. This project is based on Automation process which gives the best path for the army to follow during war times by using the A* algorithm Roles & Responsibilities:

1. Implemented A* algorithm, unit testing & debugging of the applications and closing defects raised by testing team



Contact Information:

Phone: +91-9342465678

Email:suhaas.mohandos1984@gmail.com

Location: Bengaluru, India

Education:

2006-2008

University of Southern California, USA Viterbi School of Engineering Master of Science(MS) Computer Science

2002-2006

Anna University, India
Sri Venkateswara College of Engineering
Bachelor of Engineering(BE)
Electronics & Communication

Skills:

- JDBC, Servlets, JSP, SOA, Web Services
- Java
- DSA
- Spring(Core)
- Spring MVC
- Spring AOP
- Spring Boot
- Spring Cloud
- Hibernate
- Rest API
- Oracle, MySql
- Eclipse
- HTML,XML, JSON
- Git, Gitlab